[
    {
      "question": "我们要____地看待问题。",
      "answer": "辩证",
      "options": ["了解", "辩证", "成功", "情况"]
    },
    {
      "question": "这场运动要____旧体制。",
      "answer": "颠覆",
      "options": ["影响", "颠覆", "了解", "机会"]
    },
    {
      "question": "他____了这句话。",
      "answer": "推敲",
      "options": ["推敲", "成功", "机会", "决定"]
    },
    {
      "question": "这个计划有____性。",
      "answer": "前瞻",
      "options": ["前瞻", "成功", "了解", "重要"]
    },
    {
      "question": "这个制度有许多____。",
      "answer": "弊端",
      "options": ["弊端", "机会", "情况", "影响"]
    },
    {
      "question": "事情很____复杂。",
      "answer": "错综",
      "options": ["错综", "了解", "机会", "努力"]
    },
    {
      "question": "他____后决定。",
      "answer": "深思熟虑",
      "options": ["机会", "推敲", "深思熟虑", "辩证"]
    },
    {
      "question": "我们要____利弊。",
      "answer": "权衡",
      "options": ["权衡", "决定", "了解", "影响"]
    },
    {
      "question": "我们要____解决问题。",
      "answer": "循序渐进",
      "options": ["重要", "成功", "了解", "循序渐进"]
    },
    {
      "question": "这个村庄____。",
      "answer": "自给自足",
      "options": ["自给自足", "需要", "了解", "影响"]
    }
  ]
  